<FTL>
	
<event name="FR_START_TARTARUS">
	<metaVariable name="fr_juke_tartarus" op="set" val="1"/>
	<variable name="loc_unique_sectors" op="add" val="1"/>
	<modifyPursuit amount="-15"/>
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_fr_tartarus_start" global="false">
		<color r="252" g="252" b="252" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text load="FR_TEXT_START_TARTARUS"/>
	<img back="FR_SECTOR_START_TARTARUS" planet="NONE"/>
	<hiddenAug>FR_UNSLOTED_GHOSTS</hiddenAug>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<textList name="FR_TEXT_START_TARTARUS">
	<text>The jump into Tartarus was long and difficult, seeming to take ages. What you see on the other end of your journey can only be described as... bizarre. Multiple blue stars surround you in a perfectly circular pattern, but they seem to emit no discernible signs of radiation. Your comms struggle under the might of thousands of hails from all directions, all points in space and time, being sent every second, their contents being only horrific screams and pleas for help. You decide to mute the ship's radio, an act which notably takes several attempts.</text>
</textList>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_LOAD">
	<loadEventList seeded="false" first="true">
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS" req="FR_REQUIREMENT_COMPLETED_TARTARUS_AND_IS_CHAOS" lvl="1"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES" req="FR_REQUIREMENT_COMPLETED_TARTARUS_AND_IS_CHAOS" lvl="0" max_lvl="0"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES">
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_in_progress" op="set" val="1"/>
	<loadEventList seeded="false" first="true" default="FR_TARTARUS_EMPTY">
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_1" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression" lvl="0" max_lvl="0"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_2" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression" lvl="1" max_lvl="1"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_3" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression" lvl="2" max_lvl="2"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_4" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression" lvl="3" max_lvl="3"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_5" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression" lvl="4" max_lvl="4"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_6" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression" lvl="5" max_lvl="5"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_EMPTY" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression" lvl="10"/>
	</loadEventList> 
</event>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_FINAL_BOSS_LOAD">
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_fr_tartarus_final" global="true">
		<color r="255" g="0" b="0" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Location of the final bounty, it seems to only be available after all the other bounties are done first.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>Location of the final bounty.</visitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<revisitEvent>FR_TARTARUS_FINAL_BOSS_LOAD</revisitEvent>
	<loadEventList seeded="false" first="true" default="FR_TARTARUS_EMPTY">
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_FINAL_BOSS_CHAOS" req="FR_REQUIREMENT_COMPLETED_TARTARUS_AND_IS_CHAOS" lvl="1"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_FINAL_BOSS" req="FR_REQUIREMENT_COMPLETED_TARTARUS_AND_IS_CHAOS" lvl="0" max_lvl="0"/>
	</loadEventList> 
</event>

<!--first encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_SLIMER" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_REVENANT_SLIMER">
	<destroyed load="FR_REVENANT_SLIMER_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_REVENANT_SLIMER_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="slug" prop="0.40"/>
		<crewMember type="slug_saboteur" prop="0.60"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_1">
	<text>After figuring out where you are and what you're here to do, you check your list of bounties. Six of the seven entries have been mysteriously populated with information, with the seventh remaining blank. With no other leads, you begin to parse the document, revealing your first target: Slimer, the long-dead spirit of a Slug king.

	Slimer was known throughout the Multiverse as the biggest glutton there ever was, a fact that they wore proudly. They were laid low by a batch of hallucinogenic melons, sending them into a deep coma from which they never recovered. Nobody chose to help them, on account of how rude, selfish, and vengeful Slimer could be in life. As you finish reading the entry, you look up to see a gigantic vessel out of the viewport, composed entirely out of Slug repair gel!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_SLIMER" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail the vessel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You decide to turn your comms back on, praying the voices would no longer haunt you. To your surprise, only sweet silence lies on the other end, though the view on your screen is... rather concerning. A luminous figure in the shape of a filthy, yet exquisitely-dressed Slug stares back, in an almost trance-like haze. You knew the Spook Chasers said these guys were indeed the souls of the dead, but you couldn't possibly have expected them to be right after all!</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Slimer...?</text>
				<event>
					<text>The vibrant green spirit begins to jump up and down, as if they were a child in a candy store, and emits a form of preternatural screeching that your translator can barely keep up with. "...hun... gry... I must... f-food! Food! I haven't... had food for... f-for centuries!" The feed cuts before you can even respond, and you hear the sound of a teleporter locking onto your ship. Battle stations!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>	
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice req="fr_gozer" blue="true" hidden="true">
				<text>(Goziodeon) "Who are you pretenders?! We are the only Rivals to the Spook Chasers in this town! Scram!"</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Slug simply chuckles, briefly breaking out of their starving daze, before emitting a form of preternatural screeching that your translator can barely keep up with. "...hugh-... y-your little... organization meansss... nothing here! I will... I will do my master a favor and... devour your little gassseousss body!" The feed cuts before you can even respond, and you hear the sound of a teleporter locking onto your ship. Battle stations!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>	
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_REVENANT_SLIMER_DEFEAT">
	<text>After a grueling battle, the gelatinous vessel has finally met its fate. You can only hope its captain's spirit has been put to rest in the process, as you sift through the wreckage for valuable scrap metals.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you prepare to jump to your next target, Slimer manifests himself aboard your ship. With guns pointing from every crewmember, the ancient king surrounded, he speaks. "...you... Y-you ended... h-hunger!"

			Your crew drop their blasters as the Slug raises their empty hands. "Oh... oh, glorious savior! You are truly... a kind heart beyond me! The spell, it binds me. I cannot help now, but... I will see what I can do, savior!"
			
			The next bounty seems to warn you that the target will be immune to ion damage.</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_REVENANT_SLIMER</unlockCustomShip>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--second encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_PHYS" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_REVENANT_PHYS">
	<destroyed load="FR_REVENANT_PHYS_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_REVENANT_PHYS_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="shell" prop="0.15"/>
		<crewMember type="shell_guardian" prop="0.15"/>
		<crewMember type="shell_mechanic" prop="0.15"/>
		<crewMember type="shell_scientist" prop="0.15"/>
		<crewMember type="shell_radiant" prop="0.40"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_2">
	<text>Next up on the shopping list, is Phys. According to your bounty list, she was a Shell who suffered from a cocktail of congenital diseases. The scientists in charge of her birth didn't want to give up on her, seeing her illness as a challenge to be overcome. So, to keep her heart at a steady rhythm, they infused her body with electric power.

	While her physical form may have been spared, the pain of the process drove Phys mad, causing the Shell to enter a rampage throughout the breeding facility. Mere minutes of life were cut short when the local security team was forced to gun her down. Her soul can no longer move on, not with the excruciating suffering still coursing through her very being.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>As soon as you finish reading her bounty, you spot your target already barreling towards you. Cyan power crackles along the ship's hull, arcing electricity obliterating nearby chunks of debris as the vessel moves into attack position, refusing all hails. Prepare for battle!</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_PHYS" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_REVENANT_PHYS_DEFEAT">
	<text>The Shell vessel splits into several pieces, the energy racing along its hull fading into nothing. You wonder if there were others like Phys, victims of the Shells trying a little too hard.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your train of thought is interrupted by Phys manifesting directly on your bridge, just as Slimer did earlier, and you get a good look at her for the first time. The ghost is on the smaller side, with several cracks running down her shell, all pulsating with electricity as she tilts to the side.

			"You... s-save friend! Help... save thhhhhhe othhhhhers!" Phys' voice is filled with static, and her speech is very crude, but you do get an idea of what she's imploring you to do before she fades away... if you could save Slimer and Phys from this, then maybe the other souls could be saved!</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_REVENANT_PHYS</unlockCustomShip>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--second encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_ALEENOR" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_REVENANT_ALEENOR">
	<destroyed load="FR_REVENANT_ALEENOR_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_REVENANT_ALEENOR_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="engi" prop="0.30"/>
		<crewMember type="mantis" prop="0.30"/>
		<crewMember type="mantis_suzerain" prop="0.40"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_3">
	<text>Knowing your next target will likely be just as hostile at first sight, you ready your ship before reading the next entry. Aleenor, a legendary Bishop of the Mantis Hive, revered even amongst her peers and her enemies as one of the most skilled and dangerous hunters in the Multiverse.

	Something sticks out to you - her bounty does not make any mention of trauma or unfinished business that could potentially lead her to linger after death. As you close your third bounty, you find both your FTL and Multiverse drives are on the fritz, trapping you at the beacon! It seems you're in too deep to turn back now...</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Aleenor's vessel does not appear immediately to you, and you have to chase the bright pink vessel down, forcing the Bishop to hail. "Ah, a Renegade...! I hoping not to see you, on... important mission! Given by Queen..." She pauses for a second, as if struggling to remember. "...Queen... Queen Latrakkpkat! Yes, important mission indeed! Sorry in advance. Don't have time to spare!" Her weapons power on, and any further attempts to hail her are met with radio silence.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_ALEENOR" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_REVENANT_ALEENOR_DEFEAT">
	<text>Bishops are truly formidable, especially this one, but you manage to triumph. Violet pheromones and scintillating pieces of room spread out into space.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>You brace yourself for another manifestation, seeing as how the last two appeared to you following combat. Like clockwork, the Mantis appears on your bridge, her expression one of... relief.

			"Kind soul...! I hear stories about how formidable Renegades can be, and... it warms heart to know I wasn't misled." She is oddly fluent in your tongue, which helps ease communication. "If... you have question, I can answer about me! Though... I am bound to stay silent about Tartarus... a foul necromantic spell, from one who saved me."</text>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Who are you, exactly?</text>
					<event>
						<text>The Mantis bows to you with great pride. "My name is Aleenor Lakitrapikk. Before death, I serve Queen Latrakkpkat, the greatest Queen to grace our empire! In the Hive, I made my home... I must have raised and trained thousands of Mantis, most of which eventually become Suzerain!"</text>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>How did you end up like this?</text>
							<event>
								<text>Aleenor's pride vanishes in an instant, replaced by a sensation of grief. "I died as I lived. Protecting eggs, and hatchlings! Incubators failed, make fire in the chamber, and... well, Mantis claw not meant to hold fire extinguisher. There not enough time to save both me and them... so, I chose them."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>My condolences.</text>
										<event>
											<text>The Bishop simply smiles and nods, speaking with an eerie amount of literacy. "We all must die someday, Renegade. I am simply happy my death wasn't for nothing. Regardless... you have aid from me when you need! Can't tell when your journey will end, but... I want to be with you when it does."</text>
											<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_REVENANT_ALEENOR</unlockCustomShip>
										</event>
									</choice>
							</event>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--fourth encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_VIN" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_REVENANT_VIN">
	<destroyed load="FR_REVENANT_VIN_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_REVENANT_VIN_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="rock" prop="0.40"/>
		<crewMember type="rock_crusader" prop="0.60"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_4">
	<text>You prepare your ship for combat as you jump towards your next target, thinking over what Aleenor said about a "necromantic spell", and what Phys said about "saving friends". Perhaps these lost souls... aren't here by choice? Whatever is forcing them to hold on must be here somewhere.

	Next up on the chopping block is Vin, a Paladin in service of the ever-so-stalwart Theocracy. Apparently, his death came when he forgot to turn off his ship's autopilot before going to bed, sending his vessel careening into the local sun. Understandably, such a death was something he'd probably be mad at.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Well, that isn't disturbing at all.</text>
		<event>
			<text>As usual, once you finish reading your entry, you spot a fearsome Rock vessel in front of you, its armor plates glowing as if they were made of lava. Its weapons are ablaze, and its comms are silent. No time to waste on formalities!</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_VIN" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_REVENANT_VIN_DEFEAT">
	<text>Next verse, same as the first. Another mighty ship taken down and another soul freed from whoever is keeping them here.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>This time, you don't even need to wait for Vin to show up; he's already in your quarters when you return for a short rest. With one arm, he immediately pins you to the wall, scowling out a message as a long, luminous crack down his left eye burns itself into your vision.

			"Federation dog. I do not care about your mission, or your cause. All I care about is kicking the teeth out of that Crystal-damned necromancer keeping all of us trapped under her finger. So, I will remain close until the deed is done - or, until you die, leaving me free to commandeer your ship, whichever comes first. Then, I will accompany you to the end of your pathetic little errand, if only because it is a fair trade. Understood?"
			
			You nod, Vin grins and lets go of you, leaving the room as he speaks "Good, now get back to work, this ship isn't going to fly itself".</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_REVENANT_VIN</unlockCustomShip>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--fifth encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_CLEO" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_REVENANT_CLEO">
	<destroyed load="FR_REVENANT_CLEO_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_REVENANT_CLEO_DEFEAT"/>
	<triggeredEvent event="FR_REVENANT_CLEO_DEFEAT" thisFight="true">
		<enemyCrew amount="0" includeClonebay="true"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_5">
	<text>As the stars swirl outside during your FTL jump, your mind races with the possibilities of who this necromancer could be. Why... and, how, did she summon the spirits of the dead? Is she just as much a victim of something as they are? You have to put your thinking on hold for a moment, for your fifth target is ready.

	According to your handy ghost guide, this is Cleo, an MFK Ace in life. He developed a love of all things drone and automated in his time with the Rebellion, which made it all the more ironic when he was tortured to death by a modified repair drone. Now, it is said that he has developed a form of Stockholm syndrome, despising all flesh-and-blood life.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Just as you expected, Cleo's vessel is ready for you. A powerful Rebel ship, painted in dark blue colors with an ethereal pattern shimmering across its surface, lies in wait, ready to strike.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_CLEO" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_REVENANT_CLEO_DEFEAT">
	<text>The ship crumbles to pieces, with the cargo bay causing almost a hundred drones to tumble out.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression" op="add" val="1"/>
	<ship hostile="false"/>	
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>You wait for a long time, but... Cleo never appears. However, as you rest in your quarters, a small slip of paper ejects itself from the vent cover, with a hastily scribbled note on it. "stay out of the maintenance closet and we won't have a problem"</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_REVENANT_CLEO</unlockCustomShip>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--sixth encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_ZULU" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_REVENANT_ZULU">
	<destroyed load="FR_REVENANT_ZULU_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_REVENANT_ZULU_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="lanius" prop="0.40"/>
		<crewMember type="lanius_welder" prop="0.60"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_6">
	<text>Before you can even reflect on this jump, or check your bounties, your entire command center is flooded by a golden light, and a Lanius vessel makes itself known. Its hail somehow forces its way into your feed, the usual static of an empty call in Tartarus being replaced with golden religious symbols and frightening imagery flashing in sequence. On the other end of the forced call is a shining, golden Lanius Welder, standing proud like some sort of knight.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_ZULU" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Welder speaks in an imperious tone, voice booming through the speakers. "Ah, so YOU'RE the little meat-puppet who's been causing us so much trouble! Slimer, that gluttonous idiot, was supposed to devour every trace of you, but I guess he wasn't enough for you. The fact that you are here now both impresses and disgusts me!"

			Angrily eyeing you up and down, they continue. "Your vessel is nothing to scoff at, but... in the name of, and at the command of G, our lord and savior, I shall smite you down! Have at thee, brigand!" The vessel cuts comms, rather rudely, and rushes into battle.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_REVENANT_ZULU_DEFEAT">
	<text>Even though the battle took a few minutes at most, around you it seems as if several eons have passed. Stars have appeared where there were none, and others have transformed into dwarves, nebulas, or vanished entirely.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Shortly after the glimmering pieces of the vessel drift away, they disappear entirely. In a blinding flash of light, the entire ship reappears without a scratch! Before you can even try to figure out how to defeat such a foe, however, its weapons fold back into the hull, and the Welder holds a hand up to silence the discussion.

			"Captain." His tone, all of a sudden, is soft, almost fatherly - very different from the initial encounter. "I understand you may be alarmed by what just happened, and so may your valiant crew! But... I simply ask you to stay for a moment, to let me explain why I'm here and... and what happened."</text>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Alright, what's going on here?</text>
					<event>
						<text>The Lanius contemplates for a moment, weighing his options. "My name is Zulu. I know, it's not a normal name for a Lanius. Though... it's more of a nickname, given to me by the one behind all of... this." Zulu frowns and looks to the side, remembering several things that you can't quite figure out. "Technically speaking... all of this is actually my fault, I'm afraid. My death is, sadly, what started this entire operation. Though... unfortunately, I can't exactly elaborate more right now, since... I'm bound not to speak of it."</text>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>So you can't give me actual answers?</text>
							<event>
								<text>"Sadly, not yet. But... I can say that the end of your journey is near. You will very soon meet the one who did this to all of us, the one who's tortured so many souls within Tartarus. I want to be there when it happens, so... please, let me come with you! Let me join the souls following you through space and time."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>It would be an honor, Zulu.</text>
										<event>
											<text>"Excellent." The Welder nods, their form dissipating as the other souls whisper words of joy around you. "Your final bounty can only be read at the exit... she cannot conceal herself if you're close to her."</text>
											<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_REVENANT_ZULU</unlockCustomShip>
										</event>
									</choice>
							</event>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--Final encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_G" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_REVENANT_G">
	<destroyed load="FR_REVENANT_G_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_REVENANT_G_DEFEAT"/>
	<deathEvent thisFight="true">FR_DEATH_G</deathEvent>
	<miniBoss sound="victory" musicDelay="-1"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="fr_commonwealth" prop="0.20"/>
		<crewMember type="obelisk" prop="0.60"/>
		<crewMember type="obelisk_royal" prop="0.20"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_DEATH_G">
	<lose text="With your Multiverse drive in tow, G is able to finally complete her plan. The Multiverse will soon know true fear."/>
</event>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_FINAL_BOSS">
	<text>The space here is extremely quiet. No lights, no movement. There's not even a jump beacon here, though you can still somehow jump here.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We have work to do still.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression" lvl="0" max_lvl="5" blue="false">
		<text>The seventh bounty entry is empty. The rest of the list must be cleared first!</text>
		<event load="OPTION_INVALID"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression" lvl="6" blue="false">
		<text>Read the final bounty.</text>
		<event load="FR_TARTARUS_FINAL_BOSS_TRUE"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_FINAL_BOSS_TRUE">
	<text>As you open your bounty list, you find the seventh entry is no longer corrupted. Opening it, however, reveals something... concerning. The entire file is promptly overwritten with thousands of unreadable characters, with vague threats and depictions of unspeakable acts interspersed through the noise. Your head begins to hurt looking at it all, crushing migraines pushing themselves into your perception.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Space and time themselves begin to fold and stretch around you as crimson light begins to fill the empty stretch of existence your vessel finds itself in. A gigantic vessel composed of black cubes with faded, red edges, partially phased out of this realm of existence, begins to manifest. Every speaker on your ship begins to emit an earsplitting hiss, interspersed with the cries of the damned, pleas for help, shouts of rage. The sounds, and every screen on your ship, are all shot through with one word, which imprints itself into your very mind just by looking at it.

			"BEG."</text>
			<changeBackground>FR_SECTOR_G_TARTARUS</changeBackground>
			<ship load="SHIP_FR_REVENANT_G" hostile="false"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Beg.</text>
					<event>
						<text>You drop to your knees, begging for it to stop. As your crew follow suit, the maddening stimulus subsides, revealing a cube-shaped alien on your viewscreen. Her single eye stares into your very being, as if her gaze was a thousand knives driven into your heart, and she speaks in a commanding, yet melancholic tone.

						"It seems you've finally found who you're looking for. How... quaint! To be frank, I expected a foe far more impressive than... this. I've spent eons thinking about what my final showdown would look like, and I've always wanted it to be something... climactic. Another Royal? A Crystalline queen? Perhaps the Lanius King himself, so ancient as he is. It seems, however... that I'm... stuck with you."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">	
							<text>"G... Please, you must stop all this, allow this mortal to free you from your curse, please!"</text>
								<event>
									<text>Zulu manifests himself on your bridge, to everyone's surprise. G stops for a moment, before turning to address the Lanius, the weight of a million stars lifted off of your shoulders as G turns her gaze from you. "I'm... I'm sorry, old friend. The force that compels me is greater than any of us, or all of us combined... but at least, you have recovered your mind." The alien turns back to you, the crushing gaze making you drop to your knees. "You, Renegade... you will not be so lucky."

									Zulu attempts to continue speaking, but G cuts him off. "Oh, Zulu... I know you are trying to help, but... this battle is inevitable. That god-forsaken book compels me to fight! I promise... when this battle is over, I promise I will bring you right back, all over again." G cuts the feed, her immense vessel roaring to life as the mere activation of its engines sends ripples through the fabric of reality.</text>
										<ship hostile="true"/>
										<playMusic>necronightmare</playMusic>
										<choice hidden="true">	
											<text>Continue...</text>
												<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
										</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_REVENANT_G_DEFEAT">
	<text>G's ship fights to the bitter end, and it couldn't have been more of a climactic exit. As you land the final shot to its oddly fragile hull, the chipped, broken cubes collapse into themselves, the entire ship folding into a singularity before exploding in a flash of light that threatens to shred your retinas. By the time the smoke clears, the fragments of her ship are visible again, a million tiny shards of tech you don't recognize. Finally... you've won.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression" op="set" val="10"/>
	<metaVariable name="prof_fr_bounty_completed" op="set" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<recallBoarders ship="both"/>
	<playMusic/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>You look around, the souls you've freed manifesting one by one, all of you waiting for G to appear. After a long, tense pause, the cube-shaped entity manifests herself aboard your vessel.
			      
			"It seems... what I most feared has come true. And it wasn't soon enough, though... I'm glad it ended this way, instead of the millions of other ways it could have..." G turns to Zulu, hovering in place.
				  
			"Zulu... no, everyone. I'm sorry. I am so, so sorry. I... I understand if you can't forgive me for what I've done to you all..."</text>
				<metaVariable name="fr_juke_necronightmare" op="set" val="1"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Eh, you gave us a lot of scrap. Can't go wrong with that.</text>
						<event>
						   <text>The room falls utterly silent. The Revenants all look to each other, then to you, then to G, wanting to speak about this bizarre matter.

							Phys is the first to speak, ever so chipper after you freed her from her pain. "Big cube brought Phys back... Phys happy! Phys very happy, can... can live! Live again!"

							Slimer shrugs, assuming a casual demeanor. "Eh, you gave me another ssssshot at life... or, un-life, I guesssss... and, without hunger plaguing me every waking hour. All good in my book."

							Aleenor ponders aloud. "What you did is barbaric, and... and cruel... just like Mantis. G, you make me proud!"

							Cleo is huddled in the corner of a nearby room, surrounded by drone parts, a thousand-yard stare leveled at everyone in the room. "Don't... d-don't come near my drones, any of you!"

							Vin is, understandably, very upset, having to physically restrain himself from striking G. "I'm... I'm outnumbered! Bah... fine. You get to live another day, you filthy brick. But if I EVER lay my eyes on you again... I will rip you limb from limb, until there is nothing left of you to bury." He stomps out of the room.

							Finally, Zulu chimes in, his words causing G to turn away with a mixture of joy and mild embarrassment. "Oh, how could I ever be mad at you, dear friend...? You went through so much trouble to bring me back, to bring us all back..."
						
							With the whole crowd having said what they wanted to say to G, everyone turns to you.</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
											<text>We still have a mission. Tag along, if you like!</text>
												<event>
													<text>The cube stares at you, rather shocked and befuddled. "After... after all of this, after eons of what I've done, you... still want to work with me? I'm... impressed. Flabbergasted, even. Well... I'll have an exit plan drawn up in just a moment. Thank you... Captain."</text>
													<variable name="fr_bounty_completed_mid_run" op="set" val="1"/>
													<achievement silent="false">ACH_FR_EVENT_TARTARUS</achievement>
													<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_REVENANT_G</unlockCustomShip>
													<jumpEvent>FR_G_SECTOR_SELECT</jumpEvent>
												</event>
											</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_G_SECTOR_SELECT">
	<text>You inform G that you are ready, to which she responds by nodding enthusiastically. 

	"Before I followed the dark path of necromancy, I was the Royal Navigator of the Obelisk Empire. I charted out every hyperspace lane, every optimal beacon position, every Multiversal tunnel... I even discovered the cluster phenomenon!" G's pride swells, and she tilts upwards. "My greatest invention, however... was the waystone. A way to reach anywhere, any time, regardless of your fuel, or your FTL drive's capabilities. Sadly, I was dragged into this whole mess before I could inform Queen Y, and only had time to make a single waystone... which I now entrust to you." G places a perfectly cubical device, brimming with fuchsia light, into your hands.

	"This is how we will leave this cursed place. Just set a destination in your navigation system and leave the waystone next to your engines... it'll do all the work for you!"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Thank you, G.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Don't worry about it... savior. It's the least I could do."</text>
			<choice req="fr_revenant_urn_unlocked" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Let's get out of here.</text>
					<event load="FR_REVENANT_URN_GIFT"/>
			</choice>
			<choice req="fr_revenant_urn_unlocked" lvl="1" blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Let's get out of here.</text>
					<event load="FR_WEAPON_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_REVENANT_URN_GIFT">
	<text>As you begin to dial in your destination, G stops you, offering another gift: an urn, painted a bright red with a white, pointed lid.
	
	"Savior... hold. I would like to offer you another token of my appreciation. This urn is something I've constructed in my free time, using what I've learned... it can conjure mimicries of the dead, without so much as touching their resting spirits."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Why, exactly, would I want to do this?</text>
		<event>
			<text>G laughs and shakes her ghostly arm-nubs. "Come ooooon. You know you can't pass up an opportunity for more scrap! None of you Renegades would, I imagine... though, for those who are more keen on optimizing their vessels, I'm sure the new weapons and drones these... 'apparitions'... boast will be to someone's liking."</text>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>More guns? Sign me up!</text>
					<event>
						<text>G's expression narrows, and she gives you a pat on the back. It's mildly uncomfortable, what with her limbs being cube-shaped.
						
						"That's the spirit, savior! Perhaps there are more souls yet to be found amongst the urn's power... though, only time will tell."</text>
						<metaVariable name="fr_revenant_urn_unlocked" op="set" val="1"/>
						<achievement silent="false">ACH_FR_EVENT_URN</achievement>
						<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
							<text>Got it.</text>
								<event load="FR_WEAPON_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
						</choice>
					</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_WEAPON_SELECT_TARTARUS">
	<text>"Oh, one final thing! Before you go, there's another token of gratitude I would like you to see... I've been hoarding a collection of weapons from my dear friends, and... I'll let you keep the one you like the most! That, and... I'll see what I can do to set all of them free.</text>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Slimer's bomb launcher.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Slimer grins. "You want my bomb launcher...? Well... guesssss I hope it'll ssssserve you jussssst asssss well asssss it did me."</text>
			<weapon name="FR_SLIMER_BOMB"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Phys' beam.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Phys rocks from side to side, ecstatic. "My beam! Very powerful, very shiny! Very... zappy!"</text>
			<weapon name="FR_PHYS_BEAM"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Aleenor's laser.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Aleenor waves. "The truest weapon of war. Everyone die in one shot!"</text>
			<weapon name="FR_ALEENOR_SNIPER"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Vin's missile launcher.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Vin steps back into the room, ignoring G entirely. "You... at least you have taste. This weapon was designed to melt rock and steel, do NOT waste its glory on an unfitting foe!"</text>
			<weapon name="FR_VIN_MISSILE"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Cleo's battle drone.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Cleo stammers. stepping forward. "You... want one of my drones?" He suddenly begins to shout, angrier than you've ever seen a single person in your entire life.
				
			"If I see even a single scratch on it... I will FLAY YOU ALIVE. Understood?"</text>
			<drone name="FR_GHOSTLY_DRONE"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Zulu's beam.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Zulu nods, pride swelling within him. "Ah, the Holy Pike. A weapon passed from generation to generation, now handed down to its most fitting master."</text>
			<weapon name="FR_ZULU_PIKE"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick G's cannon.</text>
		<event>
			<text>G perks up, levitating over the massive armament. "You have taste, Renegade. Though, I expected nothing less from someone like you."</text>
			<weapon name="FR_NECROMANTIC_PLASMA"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_CREW_SELECT_TARTARUS">
	<text>G sighs softly, speaking in a soft tone. "In time, I will free all of them from my old spell... but, it seems, for your mission, I'll only have time to fully free one. We'll all tag along with you, really, but... you should pick who will be able to manifest themselves."</text>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Slimer.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Slimer slides over to you, nodding as he feels the weight of a thousand galaxies lift from his spirit. "It will be an honor to ssssserve you, Captain!"

			(Press the jump button to pick a destination)</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reborn_slimer" all_skills="2">Slimer</crewMember>
			<jumpEvent>FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT</jumpEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Phys.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Phys bounces up and down as she feels the weight of a thousand galaxies lift from her spirit. "Yay! Friend picked me!"

			(Press the jump button to pick a destination)</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reborn_phys" all_skills="2">Phys</crewMember>
			<jumpEvent>FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT</jumpEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Aleenor.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Aleenor bows respectfully as she feels the weight of a thousand galaxies lift from her spirit. "I serve you as I served my Queen in life. To the very end!"

			(Press the jump button to pick a destination)</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reborn_aleenor" all_skills="2">Aleenor</crewMember>
			<jumpEvent>FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT</jumpEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Vin.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Vin simply stares at you for a moment, before shrugging. Even as the weight of a thousand galaxies lifts from his spirit, he doesn't react.

			(Press the jump button to pick a destination)</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reborn_vin" all_skills="2">Vin</crewMember>
			<jumpEvent>FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT</jumpEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Cleo.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Cleo screeches from the nearby room as he feels the weight of a thousand galaxies lift from his spirit. "Fine. Just... d-don't stand anywhere close to me!"

			(Press the jump button to pick a destination)</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reborn_cleo">Cleo</crewMember>
			<jumpEvent>FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT</jumpEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Zulu.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Zulu stretches his metallic form as he feels the weight of a thousand galaxies lift from his spirit. "It will be an honor to fight at your side, friend!"

			(Press the jump button to pick a destination)</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reborn_zulu" all_skills="2">Zulu</crewMember>
			<jumpEvent>FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT</jumpEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick G.</text>
		<event>
			<text>G shakes and shudders as she feels the weight of a thousand galaxies lift from her spirit. "You picked me... good choice. I'm sure my physical perfection had sooooomething to do with it..."

			(Press the jump button to pick a destination)</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reborn_g" all_skills="2">G</crewMember>
			<jumpEvent>FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT</jumpEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT">
	<text>You put the waystone in your engine's fuel slot and head back to the bridge to select your destination.</text>
	<variable name="loc_has_salvaged" op="set" val="0"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Union Coreworlds.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_UNION_UNIQUE">SECTOR_UNION</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_UNION_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Militia Encampment.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_MILITIA_UNIQUE">SECTOR_UNION</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_MILITIA_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Federation Sector.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_FEDERATION_UNIQUE">SECTOR_FEDERATION</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_FEDERATION_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Harmony Coreworlds.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_HARMONY_UNIQUE">SECTOR_HARMONY</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_HARMONY_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Emancipated Sanctuary.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_SEPARATIST_UNIQUE">SECTOR_SEPARATIS</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_SEPARATIST_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Ministry Capitol.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_MINISTRY_UNIQUE">SECTOR_MINISTRY</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_MINISTRY_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Gathering Gardenworlds.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_GATHERING_UNIQUE">SECTOR_GATHERING</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_GATHERING_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Free Mantis Hunting Grounds.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_FREEMANTIS_UNIQUE">SECTOR_FREEMANTIS</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_FREEMANTIS_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Imperial New-Homelands.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_IMPERIAL_UNIQUE">SECTOR_IMPERIAL</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_IMPERIAL_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Theocracy Badlands.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_OUTCAST_UNIQUE">SECTOR_OUTCAST</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_OUTCAST_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Lost Sun Stronghold.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_LOSTSUN_UNIQUE">SECTOR_OUTCAST</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_LOSTSUN_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Lanius Swarmlands.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_LANIUS_UNIQUE">SECTOR_ABANDONED_GENERIC</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_LANIUS_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Black Market.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_PIRATE_UNIQUE">SECTOR_PIRATE</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_PIRATE_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Hacked Civilian Sector.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_HACKER_UNIQUE">SECTOR_UNION</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_HACKER_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Rebel Stronghold.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_REBEL_UNIQUE">SECTOR_REBEL</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_REBEL_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Central Shipyards.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_AUTO_UNIQUE">SECTOR_AUTO</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_AUTO_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Hive Broodworlds.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_HIVE_UNIQUE">SECTOR_HIVE</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_HIVE_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Theocracy Homeworlds.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_THEOCRACY_UNIQUE">SECTOR_THEOCRACY</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_THEOCRACY_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Duskbringer Capitol.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_DUSKBRINGER_UNIQUE">SECTOR_DUSKBRINGER</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_DUSKBRINGER_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Kleptocracy Capitol.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_KLEPTOCRACY_UNIQUE">SECTOR_KLEPTOCRACY</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_KLEPTOCRACY_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Guild Territory.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_CLAN_UNIQUE">SECTOR_KLEPTOCRACY</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_CLAN_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Central Shell Nebulae.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_GENIOCRACY_UNIQUE">SECTOR_GENIOCRACY</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_GENIOCRACY_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Shell Science District.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_MORPH_UNIQUE">SECTOR_GENIOCRACY</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_MORPH_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Eargen Capitol.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_REPUBLIC_UNIQUE">SECTOR_REPUBLIC</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_REPUBLIC_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Monk Refuge.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_MONK_UNIQUE">SECTOR_UNEXPLORED_GENERIC</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_MONK_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Spectral Wastelands.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_VAGABOND_UNIQUE">SECTOR_VAGABOND</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_VAGABOND_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Spectral Capitol.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_DYNASTY_UNIQUE">SECTOR_DYNASTY</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_DYNASTY_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Coalition Stronghold.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_COALITION_UNIQUE">SECTOR_NEBULA</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_COALITION_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Confederate Coreworlds.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECTOR_CONFEDERATE_UNIQUE">SECTOR_CONFEDERATE</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECTOR_CONFEDERATE_UNIQUE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Hektar Mega-Market.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECRET_HEKTAR">SECTOR_KLEPTOCRACY</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECRET_HEKTAR</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Jerome Protectorate.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECRET_JERRY">SECTOR_REBEL</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECRET_JERRY</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Crystalline Origins.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECRET_ORIGINS">SECTOR_IMPERIAL</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECRET_ORIGINS</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Brood Stronghold.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECRET_SPIDER">SECTOR_PIRATE</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECRET_SPIDER</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Wentworth Innovations HQ.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECRET_ESTATE">SECTOR_AUTO</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECRET_ESTATE</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go to the Royal Kleptocracy Nebulae.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECRET_NIGHTS">SECTOR_KLEPTOCRACY</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECRET_NIGHTS</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="FR_REQUIREMENT_POSSIBLE_ANCIENT">
		<text>Go to the Ancient Recovery Site.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECRET_AUGMENTED">SECTOR_ABANDONED</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECRET_AUGMENTED</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="prof_opened_nexus">
		<text>Go to the Nexus Point.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECRET_SYLVAN">SECTOR_ABANDONED_GENERIC</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECRET_SYLVAN</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="FR_REQUIREMENT_POSSIBLE_ANCIENT">
		<text>Go to the Obelisk Wastelands.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECRET_ANCIENT">SECTOR_ABANDONED_GENERIC</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECRET_ANCIENT</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="prof_went_commonwealth_rift">
		<text>Go to the Commonwealth Refuge.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECRET_FR_COMMONWEALTH">SECTOR_ABANDONED_GENERIC</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECRET_FR_COMMONWEALTH</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="FR_REQUIREMENT_POSSIBLE_ANCIENT">
		<text>Go to the Obelisk Homeworlds.</text> 
			<event>
				<text>You put the coordinates and allow the waystone to do its thing.</text>
				<variable name="loc_sector_count" op="add" val="-1"/>
				<replaceSector name="SECRET_ROYAL">SECTOR_ABANDONED_GENERIC</replaceSector>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event><secretSector>SECRET_ROYAL</secretSector></event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<textList name="FR_TARTARUS_EMPTY_TEXT">
	<text>There's nothing here, not even a star in sight. You sigh as you stare out into the void, simply waiting to see how this whole G thing will turn out.</text>
	<text>The infinite blackness of space stretches as far as you can see in all directions. There is no sound out there, not even background noise on your comms.</text>
	<text>For a second, you feel like you are being watched. You, of course, see nothing when you turn around, but you keep an eye out just in case.</text>
	<text>The complete lack of anything material in your ship's general vicinity puts you on edge. You half expect stars, nebulae, perhaps even Rebel chatter... but there isn't even a fleet to worry about here.</text>
</textList>
<event name="FR_TARTARUS_EMPTY">
	<text load="FR_TARTARUS_EMPTY_TEXT"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>


<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					CHAOS!!
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS">
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_in_progress_chaos" op="set" val="1"/>
	<loadEventList seeded="false" first="true" default="FR_TARTARUS_EMPTY_CHAOS">
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_1" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" lvl="0" max_lvl="0"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_2" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" lvl="1" max_lvl="1"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_3" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" lvl="2" max_lvl="2"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_4" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" lvl="3" max_lvl="3"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_5" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" lvl="4" max_lvl="4"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_6" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" lvl="5" max_lvl="5"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_AUTO" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" lvl="6" max_lvl="6"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_SIREN" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" lvl="7" max_lvl="7"/>
		<event name="FR_TARTARUS_EMPTY_CHAOS" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" lvl="18"/>
	</loadEventList> 
</event>

<!--first encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_SMOKE" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_CHAOS_REVENANT_SMOKE">
	<destroyed load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_SMOKE_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_SMOKE_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="crystal" prop="0.40"/>
		<crewMember type="crystal_sentinel" prop="0.60"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_1">
	<text>As you jump into the next beacon, a high-pitched screech assails your senses. The gnome has begun its usual shenaniganry, but... to a level you have never seen before! Your entire ship begins to shake and spin, throwing everyone off the feet as the gnome is knocked into your hands, forcing you to clutch it for dear life as your world fades to black. When you wake up, the stars outside are red and twisted in ways that should be impossible. Even worse, all of the bounty entries in your list have been totally swapped out for entirely new individuals!
	
	After a while, you hesitantly begin to read the bounty. It tells the story of Smoke, a Crystal Sentinel. Only known by his nickname, thanks to the grayish hue shooting through his exterior, he disappeared one day after making a statement against the Empress. Rumor has it he began to hear whispers in his head that drove him mad, and was executed for his disobedience - proof of such rumors stands before you now.</text>
	 <img back="FR_SECTOR_CHAOS_TARTARUS" planet="NONE"/>
     <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Well... that sounds awfully familiar.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You eye the gnome, but it has simply returned to an inert state. Setting it down, you look up to find a huge Crystal ship staring right back at you, your comms filling with demonic whispers and static as its impossible darkness shrouds everything beyond your viewport. The hail it sends is audio-only, but you can hear the distinctive, shimmering voice of a Crystal screaming in pain as the ship raises its weapons. "The... th-the-the... the voices... the VOICES! GET OUT OF MY HEAD!"</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_SMOKE" hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_SMOKE_DEFEAT">
	<text>The Crystal vessel shatters into a number of sharp pieces, spiraling into the abyss. As you look back down to the Gnome, it has mysteriously turned in the approximate direction of your next target.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you look up, you see Smoke, standing right in front of you. His appearance, though distorted by a spiritual luminescence, is exactly as your entry described. Before you can draw your blaster, he raises his hand, simply wishing to speak.

			"Thank you, kind Renegade. Although I may have... regained my sanity... there are far more dangerous matters to talk about at this moment. If that... that gnome... is really what I think it is, then... you may have caused an irreversible chain of events to start, one which could end all things if allowed to play out, just by bringing it here." Smoke spoke in a soft, gentle tone, helping to reassure you of his turn to the light as his form begins to disintegrate into the air. "I will do my best to guide you through this sector, though... I am, sadly, bound from serving directly aboard your craft. I hope you can understand my predicament."</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_SMOKE</unlockCustomShip>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--second encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHILLS" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHILLS">
	<destroyed load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHILLS_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHILLS_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="orchid_cultivator" prop="0.30"/>
		<crewMember type="fr_snowman_smart" prop="0.70"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_2">
	<text>If what Smoke said is true, then there is no time to waste. Never mind the actual souls of the dead residing here - you need to get to the bottom of this mystery! It's not like you can leave anyway; all of your attempts to warp out of the sector by any means have failed, sometimes catastrophically, leaving completing the list as the only possible recourse. Next up on your list of targets is Chills, a Vampweed treasure hunter nicknamed for her nerves of steel.

	According to your list, she stumbled upon an ancient tome of sorts following a long, arduous expedition that killed many of her allies. When she read the tome, an eternity of maddening whispers filled her mind, rendering her catatonic and unable to divert her ship away from collision with a comet. Strangely, nobody ever found the body. Smoke sighs from all around you as he reads along... it seems he isn't the only one cursed by these whispers.</text>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your short-range sensors suddenly detect the presence of a ship - a Vampweed vessel, completely iced over, its plant components all frozen to death. Chills herself appears on the other end of the viewscreen, shivering. "C-cold... so.. cold... I... I-I, I need heat! Y-... you will do just fine!"</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHILLS" hostile="true"/>
				<status type="loss" target="enemy" system="oxygen" amount="1"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHILLS_DEFEAT">
	<text>The ship shudders, cracks, and shatters into a million pieces, something a Vampweed ship definitely should not do. Hopefully, without someone actively gunning for your body heat, you can figure out more about this place.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Before you can begin to think, you hear Smoke's voice around the ship. "Hm... I feel a sort of... power. A strange sort of... R-Renegade, watch out, watch out!"

			Chills manifests before you, looking just as shocked as you. Before you can gun her down, she shouted out. "D-don't shoot! I... t-the voices, they're... gone? I... I still feel cold, but... I can... kinda think clearly! I-I'm... sorry, Renegade..." Smoke sighs with exasperation, but Chills perks up for a moment as her form begins to dissipate, melding into the air alongside Smoke's. "Perhaps I could... help you, too? I'll tag along!"</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHILLS</unlockCustomShip>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--third encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_POK" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_CHAOS_REVENANT_POK">
	<destroyed load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_POK_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_POK_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="LIST_CREW_MORPH_RANDOM_ONLY" prop="0.30"/>
		<crewMember type="LIST_CREW_TECHNO_RANDOM_ONLY" prop="0.30"/>
		<crewMember type="LIST_CREW_MALFORM_RANDOM" prop="0.40"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_3">
	<text>Before anything can interrupt you this time, you begin to read the third bounty. A Morph, simply named Pok, forged by a particular division of Shell scientists. According to the bounty, they all gazed in wide wonder when Pok morphed themselves into a garden gnome, without even knowing what one was.

	This led to the discovery that Pok was, in a sense, the perfect Morph, able to mimic anyone down to their personal details perfectly, from nothing but a single picture. Sadly, this meant the Morph had horrifically unstable genetics, forcing them to continually switch between forms in order to prolong their tragically short lifespan.</text>
     <choice hidden="true">
        <text>But... how is that possible?</text>
		<event>
			<text>You turn to the air, ready to ask Smoke about how it could be possible, but you are interrupted by a gelatinous ship jumping in, likely captained by Pok. You receive no hail, and are instead struck by a pulse of chaotic energy that cripples a few of your ship's systems. What the hell...?</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_POK" hostile="true"/>
				<status type="loss" target="player" system="shields" amount="20"/>
				<status type="limit" target="player" system="cloaking" amount="1"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_POK_DEFEAT">
	<text>Pok's vessel splatters into a number of purple globs. You pray that this is the last time you'll have to face a ship with a clone cannon - that weapon was outlawed the moment it hit the market.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Pok manifests on your bridge almost immediately, much quicker than the other two spectres. They shape their form into a heart, then a copy of your vessel, then a handshake, then finally some sort of weird tripod alien thing, crossed out. You have no idea how a Morph can shape itself so quickly!

			Chills re-manifests on your ship, and the blob practically jumps into her arms, cooing softly. Smoke speaks from the background, resolute. "I... guess we can keep this Morph around, then."
			
			The next bounty seems to warn you that the target will have highly powerful defense drones.</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_POK</unlockCustomShip>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--fourth encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHARROR" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHARROR">
	<destroyed load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHARROR_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHARROR_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="engi" prop="0.30"/>
		<crewMember type="engi_separatist" prop="0.30"/>
		<crewMember type="engi_defender" prop="0.40"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_4">
	<text>You waste no time checking your next target. Charror, an Engi Defender, and one of the Harmony's most loyal. It is said they were permanently stationed near a key Link, eliminating any chance they could be separated from their central command... until, apparently, they disappeared for several days, then came back complaining of whispers and a desire to acquire a "soul".

	In the following days, Charror became an intergalactic criminal, kidnapping several humans and bleeding them dry of every last drop of their life force to forge themselves the closest thing eldritch rituals could create to an artificial soul. Implanting it within themselves utterly shattered their mind, and the Harmony was forced to put them down before they could re-integrate with the network and cause a catastrophic meltdown.</text>
     <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Reprogram a Defender? Who could have managed such a feat?</text>
		<event>
			<text>Smoke shrugs, just as confused as you are. Before you have time to ponder more, a multicolored Engi ship jumps into the beacon, its mesmerizing display of colors shining across the hull as its lights flicker violently. The ship hails you, revealing a captain whose nanomachines were actively falling apart into a prismatic miasma around their body. Charror tries to speak, but their speech is heavily marred by several error messages and angry screeches. That doesn't matter, though - the ship's guns are hot!</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHARROR" hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHARROR_DEFEAT">
	<text>The ship breaks into pieces, its nanomachines losing their color and reverting to their normal, gray tones.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Engi wastes no time appearing before you, barely able to stay stable.

			"Protocol 120: Gratitu-ZzZzZz. Support against [ERROR CODE 0x0004] is required, the SKILLS of this unit can bzZzZzZzZz of use. Unit no longer under [ERROR CODE 0x0004] control, need to honor SAVIOR izZzZz... paramount." The other apparitions just shrug, keeping an eye on Charror as their form melds with the ship.</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_CHARROR</unlockCustomShip>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--fifth encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEO" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEO">
	<destroyed load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEO_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEO_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="leech" prop="0.40"/>
		<crewMember type="leech_ampere" prop="0.60"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_5">
	<text>The next bounty on your list has the shortest entry so far. Leo, a Leech Ampere, was stationed at the boarders of the Eargen Capitol, leading a mostly unremarkable existence marked by the occasional battle with pirates or Rebels. One day, however, his life was flipped upside down by a vessel of unknown make and class, rushing towards the center of the system.

	The fight, according to Eargen intel, lasted less than ten seconds, with the entire crew having been killed in a particularly gruesome fashion. Analysis of biohazardous matter on the walls suggested that most of the crew died because their heads burst, with all of their nerve cells having been charred to a crisp. Leo was reported missing, and the ship immediately vanished following the fight; it is likely he was abducted.</text>
     <choice hidden="true">
        <text>I guess he won't be missing for long.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Smoke nods in agreement. Shortly afterwards, a Leech vessel appears in front of you, a brilliant green light radiating from its extremities. No hail, no quarter, it simply raises its weapons and opens fire.</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEO" hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEO_DEFEAT">
	<text>The lights fade into nonexistence as the ship is torn apart, its careful, curved design destroyed under your might.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Leech takes a long time to finally manifest before you and the other spectres. Although Leo doesn't speak, you feel a sense of gratitude radiating from him. He simply dissipates into the ship's ambiance, occasionally popping up from place to place in the most well-hidden spots.</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEO</unlockCustomShip>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--sixth encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_SEARAK" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_CHAOS_REVENANT_SEARAK">
	<destroyed load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_SEARAK_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_SEARAK_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="zoltan_devotee" prop="0.40"/>
		<crewMember type="zoltan_martyr" prop="0.60"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_6">
	<text>Hopefully, you will be able to get to the bottom of this whole Tartarus thing, with your list growing shorter and shorter. Your next target is Searak, one of the very first Duskbringers to join the movement, and to see combat.

	According to salvaged reports from the battle, a mysterious white vessel struck Searak's ship down, and tampered with its clonebay. The incident drove Searak to madness upon his rebirth, and he began to upload his mind to the DNA bank in an effort to spread the chaos. The captain of the ship was forced to commit suicide by steering the ship into a pulsar, annihilating all traces of it.</text>
     <choice hidden="true">
        <text>A shame we won't ever know the captain's name...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your crew, and the spirits, lower their heads in thought, before a scathing hail makes itself known as a ship powers up its weapons. It's Searak. "I see! The ones the voices warn me of have finally arrived... and not a moment too soon! Brothers, sisters, to arms, to arms!"</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_SEARAK" hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_SEARAK_DEFEAT">
	<text>The ship, and its unusually powerful clonebay, have finally been rent apart. You turn away from the command console, expecting Searak to make his presence known.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The once-proud Martyr manifests himself in front of you, his pride and vigor taken from him. "...how...? How could I have been so... easy to... manipulate? For all of my life, I... fought for what I thought was right, but... now, all I will ever be remembered as is... a lunatic. And, a traitor." The other apparitions step closer, and Smoke offers a hand to shake, which Searak takes before fading away. "I may not be able to atone, but... the least I can do is help you get through this hellscape."</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_SEARAK</unlockCustomShip>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--auto encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_AUTO" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_CHAOS_REVENANT_AUTO">
	<destroyed load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_AUTO_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_AUTO_DEFEAT"/>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_AUTO">
	<text>You wait with anticipation, eager to reveal the final bounty. Before you can pull up the page, however, the file scrambles itself as a... Rebel Auto-ship? It appears in front of you, weapons already primed, its sensor cluster glowing an ominous red as its odd, golden stripes glimmer in the light of a nearby star.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_AUTO" hostile="false"/>
     <choice hidden="true">
        <text>What the...?</text>
		<event>
			<text>None of your crew know why it's here, either. A couple of the spectres you've freed don't even recognize the ship at all, for the Rebellion wasn't even a twinkle in Vance's eye back when they were alive. It hails you, playing a simple, recorded message before moving in to strike.
			
			"Federation vessel. You have come too far, and seen too much, for your own good. You must now be eliminated to maintain operational security. Executing protocol L-3312 - for the Legion!"</text>
				<ship hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_AUTO_DEFEAT">
	<text>The Auto-ship manages to fight for a couple of minutes, even with a missing aft. As it finally begins to crumble, it desperately charges its FTL Drive in an attempt to escape, but it is stopped in its tracks by a fuel tank ignition that obliterates the entire vessel! Not much scrap is left, but the pieces that are there are chunks of extremely valuable Aether.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text> 
		<event>
			<text>A little bit of searching allows you to salvage one item that wasn't broken by the blast: the Auto-ship's black box. Charror sets to work decrypting its contents, a task that proves shockingly difficult, but they eventually manage to extract a short video clip.

			Everyone crowds around to watch nobody less than Vance Wentworth striking a deal with... something. The pixels around it are so blurry and over-compressed that identification is impossible, but you already know it can't possibly be good if Vance is directly involved. Charror also manages to dig up both the blueprints for a similar Auto-ship and data on an advanced form of emancipation grid similar to the one fielded by your foe!</text>
			<augment name="FR_ANNIHILATION_GRID_UNLOCKED"/>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_AUTO</unlockCustomShip>
			<store>STORE_FR_LEGION_AUTO</store>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--Siren encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_WATCHER" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_CHAOS_REVENANT_WATCHER">
	<destroyed load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_WATCHER_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_WATCHER_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="siren" prop="0.40"/>
		<crewMember type="siren_harpy" prop="0.60"/>
	</crew>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_BOUNTIES_CHAOS_SIREN">
	<text>With your interruption out of the way, the time has come to discover your last bounty. When you open the file, you find...

	...nothing. No tales or rumors, no information, just a single, massive line of text reading "The Watcher". As you lock eyes with the name, you feel an overwhelming pain in the back of your head, and are about to faint when Smoke catches you... the feeling is just like when you entered, and the gnome screeched out.</text>
    <choice req="gnome" lvl="1" blue="false" hidden="true">
        <text>Actually... where is the gnome?</text>
		<event>
			<text>In front of you stands the gnome... for all of one second, before it teleports away. You look up to the viewport, and immediately look away. Static and dizziness fills your mind, the mere sight of the vessel in front of you making you feel like you want to vomit... and yet, nothing comes up when you begin to dry-heave. The Watcher's eye fills every screen, whispers intruding on every corner of your mind and the minds of everyone aboard, everyone finally knowing what has tormented the ghosts for so long.

				Your final target is truly unlike any other, its form seeming to merge with the space around you. The unearthly roar of their engines echoes through your ship, despite the two of you being in space, but... the Watcher's vessel seems to slow down, instead pointing its weapons at you! Perhaps they want to leave no witnesses, you ponder for a moment, before locking eyes once more with the demonic presence and giving the command to open fire!</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_WATCHER" hostile="true"/>
				<playMusic>chaos_fight</playMusic>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
    <choice req="gnome" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false" hidden="true">
        <text>Actually... shouldn't the gnome be back by now?</text>
		<event>
			<text>In front of you stands the gnome... for all of one second, before it teleports away. You look up to the viewport, and immediately look away. Static and dizziness fills your mind, the mere sight of the vessel in front of you making you feel like you want to vomit... and yet, nothing comes up when you begin to dry-heave. The Watcher's eye fills every screen, whispers intruding on every corner of your mind and the minds of everyone aboard, everyone finally knowing what has tormented the ghosts for so long.

				Your final target is truly unlike any other, its form seeming to merge with the space around you. The unearthly roar of their engines echoes through your ship, despite the two of you being in space, but... the Watcher's vessel seems to slow down, instead pointing its weapons at you! Perhaps they want to leave no witnesses, you ponder for a moment, before locking eyes once more with the demonic presence and giving the command to open fire!</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_WATCHER" hostile="true"/>
				<playMusic>chaos_fight</playMusic>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_WATCHER_DEFEAT">
	<text>A massive gash splits across the ship's hull, tendrils of static pouring out of it before the abominable excuse for a space-worthy ship explodes, disintegrating into nothing but dust right in front of your eyes.</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" op="add" val="1"/>
	<playMusic/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Nobody on your ship celebrates. Nobody even comes to discuss the fight. Everyone is utterly silent, their once boisterous personalities replaced with a blank void... even the ghosts, who seem to have completely vanished. Even you feel empty inside, as if your very soul had been ripped from your physical body.

			You are able to trace the Watcher's intended jump coordinates... perhaps that may lead you to the cure for this emptiness, and perhaps the end of this wild journey.</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_WATCHER</unlockCustomShip>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--LEGION FLAGSHIP ENCOUNTER-->
<ship name="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEGION_FLAGSHIP" auto_blueprint="FR_BOSS_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEGION_FLAGSHIP">
	<destroyed load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEGION_FLAGSHIP_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEGION_FLAGSHIP_CREWKILL"/>
	<miniBoss sound="victory" musicDelay="-1"/>
	<triggeredEvent event="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEGION_FLAGSHIP_CREWKILL" thisFight="true">
		<enemyCrew amount="0" includeClonebay="true"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
</ship>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_FINAL_BOSS_CHAOS">
	<text>The space here is filled only with maddening laughter, whispers tailored to your very core memories intruding on your mind.

	There is an exit beacon here, but... it appears rotten, crumbled. There truly seems to be no way out of here, though... perhaps clearing your bounty list could give you a pointer.</text>
	<revisitEvent>FR_TARTARUS_FINAL_BOSS_CHAOS</revisitEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We have work to do still.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" lvl="0" max_lvl="7" blue="false">
		<text>The exit beacon is empty. The list must be cleared first!</text>
		<event load="OPTION_INVALID"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" lvl="8" blue="false">
		<text>Remain at the beacon. This is where the Watcher wanted to go!</text>
		<event load="FR_TARTARUS_FINAL_BOSS_CHAOS_TRUE"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_FINAL_BOSS_CHAOS_TRUE">
	<text>Although it isn't the absolute assault upon your senses the Watcher was, the vessel which jumps into combat range is no less fearsome. An older model of Rebel Flagship, retrofitted with technology you can barely understand, and painted in the same bizarre colors as the Auto-ship you ran into earlier! Hailing you from the bridge is none other than Vance Wentworth, Admiral of the Rebel Fleet.

	"Well, well... if it isn't the little Federation ship that could." Vance hisses, briefly turning and smiling to a bound and gagged individual in the corner flanked by two Rebel soldiers in unidentifiable armor. "After finding out what you did to my little drone, I had a feeling I'd have to do this myself... it seems my business partner was no trouble for you."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEGION_FLAGSHIP" hostile="false"/>
	<img back="FR_SECTOR_G_TARTARUS" planet="NONE"/>
	<playMusic>showdown</playMusic>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Wait, if you're Vance... then who's... that?</text>
		<event>
			<text>Vance grins ear to ear, as if he had just watched a planet full of Orchid children burn to the ground. He doesn't answer your question.

			"Oh! I see you want an explanation. Something to satisfy your gluttonous little mind, no...? No! No, no, NO! I will give you nothing to feast upon. I have waited DECADES to get the ball rolling here. And, now that I have both you and my little friend here right where I want them... it's time to execute. I won't let a pitiful little maggot like you stop me from doing everything I've ever wanted to do! Oh, you pansy little ghost-kisser, I hope you put up a fight. It'll be all the more worth it to watch... you... squirm!"</text>
				<ship hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEGION_FLAGSHIP_CREWKILL">
	<text>You have picked the flagship clean of all of its crew, aside from the restrained man on the bridge. Before you can breathe a sigh of relief, the ship sputters to life, activating an automated setting!</text>
	<ship hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEGION_FLAGSHIP_DEFEAT"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_CHAOS_REVENANT_LEGION_FLAGSHIP_DEFEAT">
	<text>At first, it looks like the flagship could never fall. However, a great blast from the center of the vessel instantly proves you wrong. It is instantly consumed in the explosion, sending out a shockwave that nearly tears your own vessel in half!</text>
	<variable name="loc_fr_bounty_progression_chaos" op="add" val="10"/>
	<recallBoarders ship="both"/>
	<enemyDamage amount="999"/>
	<playMusic/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
			<event>
				<text>You and your crew begin to feel lighter on your feet. It seems that destroying the vessel must have lifted the Watcher's curse... at least, partially, for the spectres do not return. This must have been Vance-1, a key Vance in the Rebellion's chain of command. Why else would he command some sort of super-prototype experimental flagship?
					
				Then, something strikes you... what about the hostage in the cockpit? Thankfully, the bridge is mostly intact amongst the wreckage, having been heavily reinforced. Bringing in the piece of the ship, you carry the wounded man aboard and remove his gag to reveal... another Vance!?</text>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>...what in the...</text>
					<event>
						<text>Vance sighs, nodding. "Yes. I'm Vance. The... Vance. Vance... Prime. I-I'm afraid I know just about as much as you do, sadly. Vance-1 betrayed me, stole my pet project... which you just blew up. If... If I had to guess, Vance-1 wanted to figure out the secrets of life and death in some sort of... ultimate plan to control the Multiverse?"

						The grizzled man closes his eyes, shaking his head. "I-I was just as blindsided by this as you were!"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Give me one reason why I shouldn't gut you where you stand.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Vance groans with frustration. "I know the only way out of this place. that, and... I have the blueprints for my little flagship on file. Just... just take it..."

									He tosses you a small thumb drive, before staggering to his feet. "Whenever you're ready... just tell me when we should leave. I might as well stick around, since... I have no place in the Rebellion after that prick stole my spot."</text>
									<variable name="fr_bounty_completed_mid_run" op="set" val="1"/>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="unique_vance" all_skills="2">Vance Prime</crewMember>
									<achievement silent="false">ACH_FR_EVENT_TARTARUS_CHAOS</achievement>
									<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_FR_LEGION_FLAGSHIP</unlockCustomShip>
									<jumpEvent>FR_VANCE_SECTOR_SELECT</jumpEvent>
								</event>
							</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_VANCE_SECTOR_SELECT">
	<text>You inform Vance that you are ready to leave. He sighs, handing you a small, floating cube that pulses with fuchsia light.
	
	"Put this in your engine's fuel tank. Vance-1 probably planned on using this to strike at Universe 0 when he left Tartarus. As far as I know, this is the only tool of its kind that exists... so choose your destination wisely, Renegade."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Huh... weirdly charitable of you, Vance.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh this isn't charity, I just rather get the hell out of this place, even if that means helping you." He snarks.</text>
			<choice req="prof_fr_chaos_apparitions_unlocked" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="1" blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Well, time to pick our destination.</text>
					<event load="FR_URN_UPGRADE"/>
			</choice>
			<choice req="prof_fr_chaos_apparitions_unlocked" lvl="1" max_group="1" blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Well, time to pick our destination.</text>
					<event load="FR_WEAPON_CHAOS_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_URN_UPGRADE">
	<text>Before you can dial in the coordinates, you begin to feel faint. Slipping out of consciousness as your newly awakened crew catch your fall, you experience a bizarre vision of an urn, red with a pointed, white lid. The souls of the many friend you met on this journey swirl about, flooding the urn with their presence, before the container closes with a clock that jostles you back awake.</text>
		<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
			<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>It takes a few minutes for you to recover. As you do, you manage to get your thoughts in order, and prepare to select your destination.</text>
					<metaVariable name="prof_fr_chaos_apparitions_unlocked" op="set" val="1"/>
					<achievement silent="false">ACH_FR_EVENT_URN_UPGRADE</achievement>
					<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
						<text>Continue...</text>
							<event load="FR_WEAPON_CHAOS_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
		</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_WEAPON_CHAOS_SELECT_TARTARUS">
	<text>Suddenly, a member of your crew points towards the viewport. It seems that a number of bizarre weapons are hurtling through space, similar in appearance to many of the mysterious vessels you've just fought. They are on a collision course with a nearby sun; their speed means you will have time to select only one of them!</text>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Smoke's crystal launcher.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You are able to snag the odd weapon out of the bunch, the others streaking past your ship and into the star. All hope of retrieving them is lost.</text>
			<weapon name="FR_SMOKE_CRYSTAL_MINELAUNCHER"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_CHAOS_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Chills' flak gun.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You are able to snag the odd weapon out of the bunch, the others streaking past your ship and into the star. All hope of retrieving them is lost.</text>
			<weapon name="FR_CHILLS_SNOW_FLAK"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_CHAOS_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Pok's clone cannon.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You are able to snag the odd weapon out of the bunch, the others streaking past your ship and into the star. All hope of retrieving them is lost.</text>
			<weapon name="FR_POK_CLONE_LAUNCHER"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_CHAOS_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Charror's beam drone.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You are able to snag the odd weapon out of the bunch, the others streaking past your ship and into the star. All hope of retrieving them is lost.</text>
			<drone name="FR_CHARROR_DRONE"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_CHAOS_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Leo's battery.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You are able to snag the odd weapon out of the bunch, the others streaking past your ship and into the star. All hope of retrieving them is lost.</text>
			<weapon name="FR_LEO_BATTERY"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_CHAOS_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Searak's energy cannon.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You are able to snag the odd weapon out of the bunch, the others streaking past your ship and into the star. All hope of retrieving them is lost.</text>
			<weapon name="FR_SEARAK_ENERGY"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_CHAOS_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick the Auto-ship's laser.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You are able to snag the odd weapon out of the bunch, the others streaking past your ship and into the star. All hope of retrieving them is lost.</text>
			<weapon name="FR_LEGION_AUTO_ZENITH"/>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_CREW_CHAOS_SELECT_TARTARUS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_CREW_CHAOS_SELECT_TARTARUS">
	<text>Attached to the note is... some form of data storage drive. Deciphering it shows information on... some form of cleansing ritual. It will only work once - you will have to pick which ghost you want to bring back to cognizance, leaving the rest to be consigned to an eternity of madness.</text>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Smoke.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You and your crew hold a brief ritual, and Smoke manifests before your eyes, rubbing his head. "You... you saved me! From this day onwards... I will fight by your side, Captain, to the end of the Multiverse!"</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reformed_smoke" all_skills="2">Smoke</crewMember>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Chills.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You and your crew hold a brief ritual, and Chills manifests before your eyes, flourishing her petals. "Hahaaa, now that's what I'm talking about! C'mon, Renegade... there's always gonna be more places to discover, more treasure to find."</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reformed_chills" all_skills="2">Chills</crewMember>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Pok.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You and your crew hold a brief ritual, and Pok manifests before your eyes, wobbling with joy. "Pok!" The little Morph shapeshifts into a form just like yours and gives you a great, big hug.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reformed_pok" all_skills="2">Pok</crewMember>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Charror.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You and your crew hold a brief ritual, and Charror manifests before your eyes, their body fully composed for a single moment. "Mercy...? This unit izZzZzZz... thankful".</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reformed_charror" all_skills="2">Charror</crewMember>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Leo.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You and your crew hold a brief ritual, and Leo manifests before your eyes, finally mustering the courage to speak. "Mercy? After everything... you still want me to... live? Renegade. Consider me a true friend, then!"</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reformed_leo" all_skills="2">Leo</crewMember>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="false">	
		<text>Pick Searak.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You and your crew hold a brief ritual, and Searak manifests before your eyes, robes flapping proudly in a nonexistent wind. "In all of my years of service, to any cause, I have never seen the kind of courage you've displayed today. If I make it back home, every Duskbringer who will ever live will sing of your deeds today!</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="fr_reformed_searak" all_skills="2">Searak</crewMember>
			<choice blue="false" hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="FR_WAYSTONE_SELECT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="FR_TARTARUS_EMPTY_CHAOS">
	<text load="FR_TARTARUS_EMPTY_TEXT"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>




</FTL>