<metadata>
  <title><![CDATA[ FTL: MULTIVERSE - FORGOTTEN RACES ADDON ]]></title>
  <threadUrl><![CDATA[https://ftlmultiverse.boards.net/thread/12/forgotten-races]]></threadUrl>
  <author><![CDATA[Gabriel Cooper And HereticChurch]]></author>
  <version><![CDATA[ 16.2 ]]></version>
  <description>
<![CDATA[ 
PATCH AFTER MULTIVERSE, REQUIRES FUSION 0.1.0+ AND THE RENEGADE COLLECTION, PATCH BOTH OF THOSE BEFORE FR

This mod brings back the in-canon extinct subclass of the Ancients/Obelisks called the "Commonwealth". It adds content for the now almost extinct salt people race and a new cruiser line for the Osmians, as well as a brand new sector with unique music and a few unlocks beacons all throughout the game.

Forgotten Races also adds 146 new ships, 141 weapons and drones not counting artilleries (mostly exclusive to said ships), 54 new crews that can be found on the new ships, a revived questline with dozens of unlocks that wasn't implemented to multiverse years ago and 2 new renegade bosses, both with exclusive weapons. Those ships all have some kinda gimmick, not all of them have a very complicated one however.

(Huge thanks to Cyrus, Altzeus, DemonFusion, Alder, Kix, Pepson, Chrono, Arc, Lizzard and Julk who helped this mod a lot over the course of its development; this little addon wouldn't be nowhere near what it is now without their help)

Proofreading and rewrites by : Alder

Some combat icons made by: Alder

Mantis queen, golden Lanius and copper Lanius sprites by: Prophet of The Grand Schnitzel

Metal Lanius's miniship sprites made by : Kix

Obelisk flagship's artillery sprites made by : Kix

CEL Ion sprite made by : Kix

Sprites for the rues and Federation artilleries made by : Kix

Help with the new salt cruiser sprite by: AgentTHeKatie

Tully dialog rewrites by : slow

Golden Flak sprite made by : MISTER D, CERTIFIED MISTER

Tartarus's music (both explore and battle) as well as G's theme and the commonwealth sector music was made by: Altzeus

All 3 of the Exterminator's boss tracks were made by: Lizzard

Watcher's cruiser and enemy hull made by: woona

Salt Weapons and zulu's pike Sprites by: Alder

Spherax Eye Code by: Pepson

Grammar help by: kāne and Nissa

artillery surges code made by: Chrono Vortex

sammy sprites made by:܇Moreorlesser

Lua codes made by and with the help of: Choosechee, Julk, Pepson, RoadTrain, LoudMute, chrono, Ranhai and Arc

appending codding help by :܇Blizz/mr_easy_money

Achievement icons for the Operator, flagships (including the RUES flagship), Snowman, Osmian, salt battleship and metal pyramid ships made by: AgentTHeKatie

Works with Multiverse 5.4.X
]]>
  </description>
</metadata>